http://www.densitron.com/privacy-policy

Who is Responsible for Your Personal Data
In this Privacy Notice references including but not limited to, “Quixant, Densitron, Quixant plc, QXT”, ‘We’’, ‘’Us’’ and ‘’Our’’ refers to the Quixant plc group companies.
We determine the purposes and manner in which your personal data is collected, used and/or disclosed and managed in compliance with current UK data protection legislation.
We take the privacy and security of your personal data very seriously. This Privacy Notice outlines what personal data we may collect about you and how we may use it.
We may change this Privacy Notice from time to time. We will notify you of any changes where we are required to do so.
What Information Do We Collect and How Do We Use It?
We intend to comply with the applicable privacy regulations which apply in the territories in which We operate.
If you need to register to use this website, or complete an online form, or send us an email (e.g. to obtain email updates or ask us to send you further information and/or to send you invitations to participate in events, cooperation opportunities and surveys), then we may collect and use personal data about you such as:
Name
Company
Email address
Country of residence
Address
Telephone number
Occupation
IP address
Such information will be provided by you and is used by us in our legitimate interests to administer the website, register you for any services you have signed up to and respond to any queries or requests for information you may have by communication methods such as telephone, email, direct messaging or post.
In the event you use this website, or complete an online form, or send us an email, please review the privacy notice.
Cookies
We may also collect information about how you use the website using cookies (and other similar technologies), as part of improving the content and functionality of the website. For more information about the use of cookies please see our Cookie Notice.
Aggregate Information
We use aggregate information, which does not identify individuals, to monitor customer traffic patterns to the website and particular pages, as well as site usage, in order to help us improve the design and layout of the content.
Who Will Have Access To Your Personal Data?
Your personal data may be transferred to other Quixant group companies. We may also share your personal data with certain third parties such as: IT providers for the purposes of system development and technical support; auditors and consultants to verify our compliance with external and internal requirements; statutory bodies, law enforcement agencies and litigants, as per a legal reporting requirement or claim; and a successor or business partner to a Quixant group company in the event that it sells, divests or sets up a collaboration/joint venture for all or part of its business.
How do We Store Your Data
We will store your personal data for as long as is reasonably necessary for the purpose for which it was collected as explained in this Notice.  We may in certain circumstances retain your personal data for longer periods of time, for instance where We are required to do so in accordance with legal, regulatory, tax or accounting requirements for the territories in which We operate.  Where your personal data has been retained in order to provide you with marketing information for Our services, it will be stored by Us only until you inform Us that you do not wish to continue to receive such materials from Us.  When your personal data is no longer required We will ensure that it is securely deleted.
International Transfer
Quixant group companies and the third parties with which it operates may be based anywhere in the world, which could include countries that may not offer the same legal protections for personal data as your country of residence. Irrespective of which country your personal data is transferred, We would only share your personal data under a strict “need to know” basis and under appropriate contractual restrictions. We will take steps to ensure that any international transfer of information between Our companies or chosen third parties is carefully managed to protect your rights and interests.
How We Protect Your Information
We have in place appropriate privacy and security policies which are intended to ensure, as far as reasonably possible, the security and integrity of all Our information, including your personal data.
What are Your Rights
You may contact Quixant group companies at www.quixantplc.com at any time to request access to the personal data we hold about you, to correct any mistakes or to request deletion of the same or withdraw your consent to certain types of processing of your personal data. If such a request places Quixant group companies or its affiliates in breach of its obligations under applicable laws, regulations or codes of practice, then We may not be able to comply with your request but you may still be able to request that We block the use of your personal information for further processing. You may also have a right to data portability to another data controller under certain circumstances.
Opting Out Of Further Communications From Us
If you have elected to receive information about Our products or services, or those of other Quixant group companies and wish to opt-out of receiving such information, then you can do so by sending an email to either marketing@densitron.com or marketing@quixant.com. You should clearly state on all communications: your name, username (if any), registration details (if any) and the name of this website.
Contact Us
Contact Us
First Name
Last Name
Your Email
Your Telephone Number
Country
United KingdomAfghanistanAlbaniaAlgeriaAmerican SamoaAndorraAngolaAnguillaAntarcticaAntigua & BarbudaArgentinaArmeniaArubaAscension IslandAustraliaAustriaAzerbaijanBahamasBahrainBangladeshBarbadosBelarusBelgiumBelizeBeninBermudaBhutanBoliviaBosnia & HerzegovinaBotswanaBouvet IslandBrazilBritish Indian Ocean TerritoryBritish Virgin IslandsBruneiBulgariaBurkina FasoBurundiCambodiaCameroonCanadaCanary IslandsCape VerdeCaribbean NetherlandsCayman IslandsCentral African RepublicCeuta & MelillaChadChileChinaChristmas IslandClipperton IslandCocos (Keeling) IslandsColombiaComorosCongo - BrazzavilleCongo - KinshasaCook IslandsCosta RicaCroatiaCubaCuraçaoCyprusCzechiaCôte d’IvoireDenmarkDiego GarciaDjiboutiDominicaDominican RepublicEcuadorEgyptEl SalvadorEquatorial GuineaEritreaEstoniaEswatiniEthiopiaFalkland IslandsFaroe IslandsFijiFinlandFranceFrench GuianaFrench PolynesiaFrench Southern TerritoriesGabonGambiaGeorgiaGermanyGhanaGibraltarGreeceGreenlandGrenadaGuadeloupeGuamGuatemalaGuernseyGuineaGuinea-BissauGuyanaHaitiHeard & McDonald IslandsHondurasHong Kong SAR ChinaHungaryIcelandIndiaIndonesiaIranIraqIrelandIsle of ManIsraelItalyJamaicaJapanJerseyJordanKazakhstanKenyaKiribatiKosovoKuwaitKyrgyzstanLaosLatviaLebanonLesothoLiberiaLibyaLiechtensteinLithuaniaLuxembourgMacao SAR ChinaMadagascarMalawiMalaysiaMaldivesMaliMaltaMarshall IslandsMartiniqueMauritaniaMauritiusMayotteMexicoMicronesiaMoldovaMonacoMongoliaMontenegroMontserratMoroccoMozambiqueMyanmar (Burma)NamibiaNauruNepalNetherlandsNetherlands AntillesNew CaledoniaNew ZealandNicaraguaNigerNigeriaNiueNorfolk IslandNorthern Mariana IslandsNorth KoreaNorth MacedoniaNorwayOmanOutlying OceaniaPakistanPalauPalestinian TerritoriesPanamaPapua New GuineaParaguayPeruPhilippinesPitcairn IslandsPolandPortugalPuerto RicoQatarRomaniaRussiaRwandaRéunionSamoaSan MarinoSaudi ArabiaSenegalSerbiaSeychellesSierra LeoneSingaporeSint MaartenSlovakiaSloveniaSolomon IslandsSomaliaSouth AfricaSouth Georgia & South Sandwich IslandsSouth KoreaSouth SudanSpainSri LankaSt. BarthélemySt. HelenaSt. Kitts & NevisSt. LuciaSt. MartinSt. Pierre & MiquelonSt. Vincent & GrenadinesSudanSurinameSvalbard & Jan MayenSwedenSwitzerlandSyriaSão Tomé & PríncipeTaiwanTajikistanTanzaniaThailandTimor-LesteTogoTokelauTongaTrinidad & TobagoTristan da CunhaTunisiaTurkeyTurkmenistanTurks & Caicos IslandsTuvaluU.S. Outlying IslandsU.S. Virgin IslandsUgandaUkraineUnited Arab EmiratesUnited StatesUruguayUzbekistanVanuatuVatican CityVenezuelaVietnamWallis & FutunaWestern SaharaYemenZambiaZimbabweÅland Islands
Job Title
Company
Message
I would like to receive news, product information and offers from Densitron by email.
I consent to Densitron using my information in accordance with their privacy policy.
Close
